CHRISTOPHER OWEN PRAWIRA

SUMMARY

Meticulous university student and full-stack developer with a six-month industry placement experience effectively maintaining back-end APIs and overseeing their day-to-day maintenance and operation. A quick learner, keen on learning new technological tools and processes, and possesses great tenacity to work under pressure while always ensuring rules and standards are met

CONTACT DETAILS

- Phone: +61 452 664 517
- christopherowenprawira@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/christopher-prawirab7a190158/

AWARDS & RECOGNITION

- MAC x Hack Sprint 2021 3rd Place Winner | July 2021
- 2nd Place for Monash FHIR 2020 Programming Competition | December 2020
- 1st Place for Monash FHIR 2020 Programming Competition | July 2020
- Information Technology Industry-Based Learning (IBL) Placement Scholarship | July 2019
- Information Technology International Merit Scholarship | February 2018

SKILLS AND ABILITIES

Strong willingness to learn Attention to detail Self-Organized Good time management skills Fast learner Motivated

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Back-end API IBL Developer (Internship)

Australia Post | July 2019 - December 2019

- Maintained back-end Application Programming Interfaces (API) of Australia Post's mobile application team
- Performed optimization for Australia Post's Android app, reducing startup time by around 45%
- Technologies used include AWS, Bamboo CI/CD pipeline, Spring Boot microservice framework.

Monash Undergraduate Programming Bootcamp Tutor (Volunteer)

Monash University | August 2019 - August 2019

 Assisted new university students with transtitioning to IT and programming by introducing programming fundamentals in Python

Information Technology Peer Mentor

Monash University | March 2019 - June 2019

• Provided support and advice to students transitioning into university life

EDUCATION

Monash University

Master of Information Technology (Coursework) February 2021 - December 2022

Monash University

Bachelor of Information Technology, Software Development Major February 2018 - January 2021

• GPA: 3.875 | WAM: 83.525

Jakarta International College (JIC)

Monash University Foundation Year (MUFY)

• GPA: 4.0 | WAM: 87.75

LANGUAGES

- English
- Indonesian